【The fate that cannot be liberated】
[해방될 수 없는 운명]
[Episode 12]
[12화]
stop.
멈추다.
go.
가다.
They started arresting people again
또 사람들을 체포하기 시작했어요
[Wanted Order]
[원하는 주문]
What crime did they commit?
그들은 어떤 범죄를 저질렀나요?
go.
가다.
sorry.
죄송합니다.
I can not help you.
난 널 도울 수 없다.
I can only tell you
난 너에게만 말할 수 있어
running.
달리기.
Run as far as you can.
가능한 한 멀리 달리세요.
If someone wants to point fingers, excuses will always be found.
누군가가 손가락질하고 싶어하면 항상 변명이 발견될 것입니다.
No one can save you.
아무도 당신을 구할 수 없습니다.
get away!
저리 가!
try your best.
최고의 노력을.
Let's go now!
이제 가자!
What's wrong?
뭐가 문제 야?
are you afraid of dying
당신은 죽는 것이 두렵습니까?
Father and our brothers?
아버지와 우리 형제들?
Jiuling,
지울링,
I'm not afraid.
나는 두렵지 않다.
You will be the only one of our family to survive .
당신은 우리 가족 중 살아남을 유일한 사람이 될 것입니다 .
What are we doing here?
우리 여기서 뭐하는 거지?
- He San. Hesan. - WHO?
- 몇 세. 몇 세. - WHO?
hurry. He is a fugitive from the He family.
서두르다. 그는 He 가족의 도망자입니다.
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
Why did you come to Rong Mansion blatantly?
왜 노골적으로 롱맨션에 오셨나요?
When you see the jade pendant, it's like seeing the emperor.
옥 펜던트를 보면 마치 황제를 보는 것 같습니다.
You are just guardians.
당신은 단지 보호자일 뿐입니다.
how dare you!
어떻게 감히!
Aren't you afraid of offending the emperor?
황제를 화나게하는 것이 두렵지 않습니까?
All of you, stay out of my way.
모두들 내 앞을 가로막지 마세요.
This dragon pendant can only be effective for a period of time.
이 드래곤 펜던트는 일정 시간 동안만 작동할 수 있습니다.
A moment is enough.
한 순간이면 충분합니다.
Rong Yu.
유 롱.
come out. Jiuling is here to see you.
나오다. Jiuling이 당신을 만나러 왔습니다.
Master, please have some soup.
선생님, 국 좀 드세요.
Rong Yu.
유 롱.
He Jiuling is here to see you.
He Jiuling이 당신을 만나러 왔습니다.
He San, put me down.
그 산, 나를 내려 놓으십시오.
Rong Yu.
유 롱.
He Jiuling.
He Jiuling.
what's wrong with you?
무슨 일이야?
He San,
허 산,
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
where are they.
그들은 어디에 있습니까?
hurry up.
서둘러요.
Master Rong.
롱 선생님.
I will entrust Jiuling to you from now on, okay?
이제부터 Jiuling을 당신에게 맡길 게요, 알았죠?
Marry Jiuling now.
지금 Jiuling과 결혼하세요.
Do you want me to get married at a time like this?
이런 시기에 결혼하길 원하시나요?
Jiuling,
지울링,
We have no choice now.
이제 우리에게는 선택의 여지가 없습니다.
But what does it matter?
하지만 그게 무슨 상관이야?
Am I getting married?
나 결혼하는 거야?
The He family is guilty,
He 가족은 유죄입니다.
But it should not affect outsiders.
하지만 외부인에게 영향을 주어서는 안 됩니다.
outsider?
문외한?
They are in the young master's yard. hurry up!
그들은 젊은 주인의 마당에 있습니다. 서둘러요!
hurry up.
서둘러요.
They are in the young master's yard.
그들은 젊은 주인의 마당에 있습니다.
open the door. hurry up!
문을 열어라. 서둘러요!
So, you don’t want me to become a member of the He family?
그럼 내가 He 가문의 일원이 되는 것을 원하지 않는 겁니까 ?
I don't.
나는 아니에요.
hurry. Open the door!
서두르다. 문을 열어라!
Capture them and execute them immediately.
캡처하고 즉시 실행합니다.
The young master is inside. Don't hurt him.
젊은 주인이 안에 있어요. 그를 다치게 하지 마세요.
go. hurry. Open the door!
가다. 서두르다. 문을 열어라!
He Qiuting, who do you think you are?
He Qiuting, 당신은 누구라고 생각합니까?
What right do you have to prevent me from entering the He family?
내가 He 가족에 들어가는 것을 막는 당신에게는 어떤 권리가 있습니까 ?
What qualifications do you have to marry me into the Rong family?
나와 롱 가문에 결혼하려면 어떤 자격이 있어야 합니까 ?
Because I am your brother.
왜냐하면 나는 당신의 형제이기 때문입니다.
Jiuling,
지울링,
You never considered me your brother,
당신은 나를 당신의 형제라고 생각한 적이 없습니다.
You never called me brother either.
너도 나한테 형이라고 부르지 않았잖아.
But my father and brothers are not here,
하지만 아버지와 형제들은 여기에 없고,
You must listen to me.
당신은 내 말을 들어야합니다.
Rong Yu,
유 롱,
Regarding past marriage contracts,
과거의 결혼계약에 관해서는,
It's our fault.
그건 우리 잘못이에요.
We owe you an apology.
우리는 당신에게 사과할 의무가 있습니다.
Do you still want to
아직도 하고 싶나요?
spend the rest of your life
남은 인생을 보내세요
Together with He Jiuling, we will never be separated again?
He Jiuling과 함께 우리는 다시는 헤어지지 않을 것입니까?
Open the door!
문을 열어라!
Then you kneel with her now in front of heaven and earth
그렇다면 당신은 지금 하늘과 땅 앞에 그녀와 함께 무릎을 꿇고 있습니다.
Is it okay to marry her?
그 사람과 결혼해도 괜찮을까요?
I do not want.
하고 싶지 않다.
hurry. Turn it on!
서두르다. 전원을 켜십시오!
open the door. Turn it on. hurry up!
문을 열어라. 전원을 켜십시오. 서둘러요!
open the door. hurry. open the door.
문을 열어라. 서두르다. 문을 열어라.
He San.
그 산.
open the door.
문을 열어라.
Jiuling,
지울링,
I once told you,
내가 한 번 말했잖아,
If you want to rob, I will help you dispose of the stolen goods.
도둑질을 하고 싶다면 훔친 물건을 처리하는 것을 도와드리겠습니다.
If you want to steal flowers, I will spy on you.
꽃을 훔치고 싶다면 내가 당신을 감시하겠습니다.
If you want to kill someone, I will hide the body for you.
누군가를 죽이고 싶다면 시체를 숨기는 것을 도와 드리겠습니다.
But now you are going to be killed
하지만 이제 당신은 죽임을 당할 것입니다.
I'll block your way.
당신의 길을 막겠습니다.
I'm so useless.
나는 너무 쓸모가 없습니다.
I couldn't save my father.
나는 아버지를 구하지 못했습니다.
I can't save my brother and sister-in-law.
나는 형수 와 형수를 구할 수 없습니다 .
He San!
그 산!
I can at least save you.
나는 적어도 당신을 구할 수 있습니다.
Today is my sister's wedding.
오늘은 내 여동생의 결혼식이다.
Welcome to the ceremony.
행사에 오신 것을 환영합니다.
catch him!
그를 잡아!
Rong Yu,
유 롱,
Please take good care of Jiuling.
Jiuling을 잘 돌봐주세요.
She always thinks she is smart
그녀는 항상 자신이 똑똑하다고 생각해요
But she is actually very naive.
그러나 그녀는 실제로 매우 순진합니다.
And her willpower is particularly strong.
그리고 그녀의 의지력은 특히 강합니다.
No matter how much pain she has, how painful it is,
그 사람이 아무리 고통스러워도, 그것이 얼마나 괴로워도.
She won't cry for herself.
그녀는 자신을 위해 울지 않을 것입니다.
Her will is so strong.
그녀의 의지는 너무나 강합니다.
She only shed tears for you
그 사람은 당신을 위해서만 눈물을 흘렸어요
in the past.
과거에.
Don't make her cry again.
그녀를 다시 울게 만들지 마세요.
Master.
주인.
What does it matter if she is wanted by the courts?
법원이 그녀를 수배한다면 무슨 상관이겠는가?
do you really want her to die
당신은 정말로 그 사람이 죽기를 바라나요?
Make the young master sad?
젊은 주인을 슬프게 만들까요?
-Jiu Ling. - Stay out of my way.
-지우 링. - 방해하지 마세요.
This is very dangerous. Stop the young master from coming forward.
이것은 매우 위험합니다. 젊은 주인이 앞으로 나오는 것을 막으십시오.
- Young master. - Jiuling.
- 젊은 스승님 - Jiuling.
He Jiuling.
He Jiuling.
Jiuling. Jiuling.
지울링.지울링.
You will be the only one of our family to survive .
당신은 우리 가족 중 살아남을 유일한 사람이 될 것입니다 .
Don't let my death be in vain.
내 죽음을 헛되게 하지 마세요.
I beg you.
부탁드립니다.
Kneel down for you.
당신을 위해 무릎을 꿇으세요.
hurry up.
서둘러요.
Kowtow first.
먼저 Kowtow.
Master, hurry up. Kneel down with Miss He.
선생님, 서두르세요. Miss He와 함께 무릎을 꿇으세요.
To heaven and earth.
하늘과 땅으로.
Kowtow for the second time.
두 번째로 Kowtow.
To my brothers.
내 형제들에게.
Master, hurry up.
선생님, 서두르세요.
Father. Father. Father.
아버지. 아버지. 아버지.
- I will kill you - Father.
- 죽여버리겠어요 - 아버지.
Dad, if you leave her with a scar, my brother-in-law will ask for a return.
아빠, 상처난 채로 놔두면 형부가 돌려달라고 할 거예요.
Father, stop being confused. Father.
아버지, 혼란스러워하지 마세요. 아버지.
Father.
아버지.
How would you like to style your hair?
헤어스타일을 어떻게 하시겠습니까?
I'm going to study.
공부 할거야.
From now on, you can sit here every morning
이제부터 매일 아침 여기 앉아도 돼
I'll comb your hair.
내가 머리를 빗어줄게요.
Third brother!
셋째 형님!
Anyway, I helped you with something.
어쨌든, 내가 뭔가를 도와줬어.
When siblings work together, their power can cut through metal.
형제자매가 함께 일하면 그들의 힘은 금속을 절단할 수 있습니다.
I will definitely protect you.
나는 반드시 당신을 보호할 것입니다.
Make sure you are happy and carefree.
당신이 행복하고 평온한지 확인하십시오.
He Jiuling.
He Jiuling.
Get He Jiuling.
He Jiuling을 잡아라.
Yes.
예.
The young master and young lady have just completed the ceremony.
젊은 스승님과 아가씨가 방금 의식을 마쳤습니다.
Who dares to harm the young lady?
누가 감히 젊은 아가씨에게 해를 끼치겠습니까?
You can't take my wife away.
당신은 내 아내를 데려갈 수 없어요.
Master, your marriage is just child's play.
스승님, 당신의 결혼은 그저 어린아이 장난일 뿐입니다.
Zhan Ping said, the ceremony is completed and we are husband and wife.
잔핑은 "결혼식은 끝났고 우리는 부부가 됐다"고 말했다.
You can't take my wife away.
당신은 내 아내를 데려갈 수 없어요.
The He family was sentenced to genocide.
He 가족은 대량 학살을 선고 받았습니다.
Even if you are married,
결혼을 했어도,
This still happened after the verdict.
이런 일은 판결 후에도 계속 발생했습니다.
He Jiuling must be taken away by order of the Ministry of Punishment.
형벌부의 명령에 따라 He Jiuling을 데려가야 합니다.
Don't you think she can be acquitted?
그녀가 무죄 판결을 받을 수 있다고 생각하지 않나요?
By dishonest measures.
부정직한 조치로.
Yong adult,
용인,
do you agree?
동의하시나요?
uncle.
삼촌.
Then you should take me with you.
그럼 당신도 나를 데리고 가야 해요.
I am already married to He Jiuling.
저는 이미 He Jiuling과 결혼했습니다.
I am also a member of the He family now.
나도 이제 He 가족의 일원이 되었습니다.
Well.
잘.
Lord of Song Dynasty.
송나라의 군주.
Yes.
예.
They did get married in a hurry.
그들은 서둘러 결혼했습니다.
But the engagement was already set.
그러나 약혼은 이미 정해져 있었습니다.
He Jiuling is from the Rong family.
He Jiuling은 Rong 가족 출신입니다.
She shouldn't bear the sins of the He family.
그녀는 He 가문의 죄를 담당해서는 안 됩니다.
Yong adult,
용인,
Why are you so confused?
왜 그렇게 혼란스러워요?
Back then, He Jiuling ran off to Nanjiang.
당시 He Jiuling은 Nanjiang으로 도망갔습니다.
Everyone knows
다들 아시죠
She is running away from marriage.
그녀는 결혼을 앞두고 가출 중이다.
Now she's taking advantage of the engagement
이제 그녀는 약혼을 이용하고 있습니다
Save her life.
그녀의 생명을 구하십시오.
How heartless she is.
그녀는 얼마나 무정한가.
How could you let her do this!
어떻게 그녀가 이런 일을 하도록 놔둘 수 있단 말인가!
So, do you also want to take Yu with you?
그럼 유우도 데리고 갈래?
I will never take the young master with me.
나는 결코 젊은 스승을 데리고 가지 않을 것이다.
He was just acting impulsively now.
그는 지금 충동적으로 행동하고 있을 뿐입니다.
after a while,
잠시 후,
He would definitely forget her.
그는 분명히 그녀를 잊었을 것이다.
I'm afraid he won't.
나는 그가 그렇게 하지 않을까봐 두렵다.
Zhanping, go take care of Heshan.
Zhanping, 가서 Heshan을 돌봐주세요.
I will take care of her.
내가 그녀를 돌볼 것이다.
Do not be afraid.
두려워 하지마.
He Jiuling.
He Jiuling.
General He,
그 장군님,
He Qiuting passed away.
He Qiuting이 세상을 떠났습니다.
This is where he belongs.
그가 속한 곳은 바로 이곳이다.
You can get this before executing.
실행하기 전에 이를 얻을 수 있습니다.
Father, what did he just say?
아버지, 방금 그가 뭐라고 말씀하셨나요?
Qiuting, what happened to Qiuting?
Qiuting, Qiuting에게 무슨 일이 일어났나요?
dd-Did he say that?
dd- 그 사람이 그렇게 말했어요?
Did he run away?
그 사람 도망갔나요?
this child
이 아이
Usually timid and afraid of pain.
보통 소심하고 고통을 두려워합니다.
He's not good at anything
그 사람은 아무것도 잘 못해요
But run away.
하지만 도망쳐.
Fortunately he escaped.
다행히 그는 탈출했다.
I always knew he could escape.
나는 그가 탈출할 수 있다는 것을 항상 알고 있었습니다.
Master, stop covering up for her.
선생님, 그녀를 위해 은폐를 그만 두세요.
The little madam has already covered herself with so many quilts.
작은 부인은 이미 이불을 너무 많이 덮었습니다.
If you cover her again, she will suffocate.
다시 덮으면 질식할 거예요.
But her hands were so cold.
하지만 그녀의 손은 너무 차가웠다.
I'll get her a hand warmer.
내가 그녀에게 따뜻한 손을 가져다 줄게요.
The hand warmer is too hot.
손난로가 너무 뜨겁습니다.
The young master knew that he would always hold her like this.
젊은 스승은 자신이 항상 그녀를 이렇게 안고 있을 것이라는 것을 알고 있었습니다.
Then holding her like this all the time is the right thing to do.
그렇다면 항상 이렇게 그녀를 안고 있는 것이 옳은 일입니다.
The quilt is too stuffy.
이불이 너무 답답해요.
You will suffocate her, Master.
당신은 그녀를 질식시킬 것입니다, 마스터.
Okay then.
그럼요.
Master,
주인,
tt-Today is not a good day.
tt- 오늘은 좋은 날이 아니네요.
I wonder if the young lady will wake up?
그 젊은 아가씨가 깨어날지 궁금해요.
By noon,
정오까지,
I'm going to pick up her family? ? ?
내가 그 사람 가족을 데리러 갈까? ? ?
what time is it now?
지금 몇 시야?
- young lady. you're awake! - you're awake!
- 아가씨. 당신은 깨어 있어요! - 일어났구나!
Prepare the horse.
말을 준비하십시오.
Yang Ying.
양잉.
sorry.
죄송합니다.
If there is another life
또 다른 삶이 있다면
I want to love you passionately.
나는 당신을 열정적으로 사랑하고 싶습니다.
You just need to say it once a day.
하루에 한 번씩만 말하면 됩니다.
I love you.
사랑해요.
Then he will be beautiful
그러면 그 사람은 아름다울 거야
It’s a pleasure to be your child.
당신의 자녀가 되어 기쁘네요.
Brother, you have to say this too.
형님, 이것도 말해야 해요.
No, I can not.
아니 난 할 수 없어.
Say it.
말해.
I love you.
사랑해요.
I love you too.
나도 사랑해요.
[Order]
[주문하다]
implement.
구현하다.
Stop the carriage.
마차를 멈추세요.
Flatten and park.
평평하게 하고 주차하세요.
A loyal soul never dies,
충성스러운 영혼은 결코 죽지 않으며,
Waiting for the day of justice.
정의의 날을 기다리며.
bid farewell,
작별을 고하다,
Father.
아버지.
Father!
아버지!
My lovely daughter!
나의 사랑스러운 딸!
Goodbye, brother and sister-in-law.
안녕히 계세요, 형님과 형수님.
How cute!
얼마나 귀엽습니까!
Goodbye, second brother and second sister-in-law.
안녕히 계십시오, 둘째 형님과 둘째 형수님.
Thanks.
감사해요.
Come on, I'm here.
어서, 나 여기 있어.
I'm not afraid of you.
나는 당신을 두려워하지 않습니다.
???Under the sunset at dusk? ? ?
???해질녘 노을 아래서요? ? ?
???I traveled thousands of miles to a distant place? ? ?
???나는 먼 곳으로 수천 마일을 여행했다고요? ? ?
???Playing the piano under the moonlight? ? ?
???달빛아래 피아노 연주? ? ?
???These drinks won’t make me forget? ? ?
???이 음료수는 잊혀지지 않을까요? ? ?
???The desire I wrote for you? ? ?
???내가 당신을 위해 쓴 소망은요? ? ?
??? Our destiny is written on paper? ? ?
??? 우리의 운명은 종이에 적혀있다고? ? ?
??? Like the strongest wine? ? ?
??? 최강의 와인을 좋아하시나요? ? ?
??? There is no way to escape fate? ? ?
??? 운명을 피할 방법은 없나요? ? ?
???Looking back, I saw you waiting? ? ?
???뒤돌아보니 기다리고 있는거 보이시죠? ? ?
???Our life is full of? ? ?
???우리 삶은 가득하다? ? ?
???With joy and sadness? ? ?
???기쁨과 슬픔으로? ? ?
???Eager for crystallization? ? ?
???결정화를 원하시나요? ? ?
???Into the bright Milky Way? ? ?
???밝은 은하수 속으로? ? ?
???I gently stroke the guzheng? ? ?
???고젱을 가볍게 쓰다듬는다? ? ?
???Waiting for a passerby like you? ? ?
???당신 같은 행인을 기다리고 있나요? ? ?
???So you are my indissoluble bond? ? ?
???그럼 당신은 나의 불용성 유대인가요? ? ?
【Rongfu】 ? ? ? So you are my indissoluble bond? ? ?
【롱푸】 ? ? ? 그럼 당신은 나의 불용성 유대입니까? ? ?
I am fine.
괜찮아요.
this is yours.
이것은 당신 것입니다.
Keep it for now.
지금은 보관하세요.
Master.
주인.
Today we are going to the astrology center. Don't forget it.
오늘 우리는 점성술 센터에 갈 예정입니다. 잊지 마세요.
Astrology Garden
점성술 정원
More beautiful than here.
여기보다 더 아름답습니다.
The wintersweet flowers bloom particularly well there.
그곳에서는 겨울에 피는 꽃이 특히 잘 피어납니다.
Heshan said, these are all
Heshan은 이것이 전부라고 말했습니다.
I planted it.
나는 그것을 심었다.
Do you want to go see them?
가서 보러 갈래?
It's not snowing outside.
밖에는 눈이 내리지 않습니다.
There are some shops open on the street.
거리에 몇몇 상점이 열려 있습니다.
Master, it will be too late if you don’t leave now.
스승님, 지금 떠나지 않으면 너무 늦습니다.
When you want to go out,
밖에 나가고 싶을 때,
Just tell me.
그냥 말해.
Madam, the prince wants to see you.
부인, 왕자님이 당신을 보고 싶어하십니다.
young lady.
젊은 숙녀.
I should be the one paying homage to you.
나는 당신에게 경의를 표하는 사람이 되어야 합니다.
I should also apologize.
나도 사과해야겠다.
I will never forget your kindness
나는 당신의 친절을 결코 잊지 않을 것입니다
He saved my third brother that day.
그날 그는 내 셋째 동생을 구해줬어요.
Why are you? ? ?
너는 왜? ? ?
The prince has dismissed my young master from the position of personal bodyguard.
왕자님은 나의 젊은 스승님을 개인 경호원 자리에서 해고하셨습니다.
He wants me to leave Rongfu
그 사람은 내가 롱푸를 떠나길 원해요
And never set foot on it again.
그리고 다시는 그 위에 발을 딛지 마십시오.
leave?
떠나다?
I'll tell the young master and Zhanping
젊은 스승과 잔핑에게 말할게요
I will go back to visit my family.
나는 가족을 방문하기 위해 다시 돌아갈 것이다.
So please keep my secret, young lady.
그러니까 비밀을 지켜주세요, 아가씨.
And after that?
그리고 나서?
Things will get better after that.
그 후에는 상황이 좋아질 것입니다.
I'm just an insignificant person.
나는 그저 보잘것없는 사람일 뿐입니다.
no one will remember me
아무도 나를 기억하지 못할 거야
after a while.
잠시 후.
Loss and gain.
손실과 이득.
Meeting and parting.
만남과 이별.
This happens all the time.
이런 일은 항상 발생합니다.
Don't blame yourself, young lady.
자신을 비난하지 마세요, 아가씨.
Nor do you ask for mercy from the Lord.
또한 주님께 자비를 구하지도 않습니다.
Otherwise, the situation could be worse.
그렇지 않으면 상황이 더 악화될 수 있습니다.
Just keep it a secret for me.
나한테는 비밀로 해주세요.
get.
얻다.
loss.
손실.
Meeting.
회의.
parting.
이별.
This happens often
이런 일이 자주 발생합니다
Only suitable for acquaintances.
지인에게만 적합합니다.
He Jiuling.
He Jiuling.
Now you are alone.
이제 당신은 혼자입니다.
If you can never fully commit to anyone again,
다시는 누구에게도 완전히 헌신할 수 없다면,
You will never experience loss and separation.
당신은 결코 상실과 이별을 경험하지 않을 것입니다.
【Remember forever】
[영원히 기억하세요]
I heard that your left hand hurts again.
왼손이 또 아프다고 들었어요.
Suffered minor injuries. This is not a problem.
경미한 부상을 입었습니다. 이것은 문제가 되지 않습니다.
It doesn't matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
I invite you to come here today
오늘 여기로 여러분을 초대합니다
Remind you of something.
뭔가를 상기시켜주세요.
I allow you to marry Rong Yu
나는 당신이 용우와 결혼하는 것을 허락합니다
So you should follow the rules here.
따라서 여기의 규칙을 따라야 합니다.
When your elders advise you, you should kneel down.
어른들이 조언하면 무릎을 꿇어야 합니다.
[Rong Zhizhi’s Lingpai]
[롱즈지의 링파이]
As a wife,
아내로서,
You should prioritize your husband.
남편을 우선시해야합니다.
If your husband doesn't come back,
남편이 돌아오지 않으면
You shouldn't eat or sleep first.
먼저 먹거나 자면 안됩니다.
When your husband is at home,
남편이 집에 있을 때,
you should take care of him
너는 그 사람을 돌봐야 해
And worried about his worries.
그리고 그의 걱정이 걱정되었습니다.
You shouldn't let him worry about you.
그가 당신에 대해 걱정하도록 놔두어서는 안 됩니다.
do you understand?
이해했나요?
Yes.
예.
when he is sick,
그가 아플 때,
You should sleep in separate beds.
별도의 침대에서 자야 합니다.
now,
지금,
Rong Yu sleeps separately from you.
Rong Yu는 당신과 별도로 자고 있습니다.
but i think
하지만 나는 생각해
people sleeping outside
밖에서 자는 사람들
It shouldn't be Rong Yu, right?
Rong Yu가 아니어야겠죠?
We'll switch back tonight.
오늘 밤에 다시 전환하겠습니다.
I don't care if you used to practice martial arts.
당신이 무술을 연습했든 상관없어요 .
but now,
그러나 지금,
Rong Yu's body is very weak.
유용우의 몸은 매우 약하다.
He couldn't stand this.
그는 이것을 참을 수 없었습니다.
Put your sword away.
칼을 치워두세요.
Forget...
잊다...
All martial arts things.
무술의 모든 것.
As for the He family’s affairs,
허 가문의 일에 관해서는,
this is your wealth
이것이 당신의 재산입니다
Survive.
생존하다.
from now on,
지금부터,
Just be the young lady you are.
그냥 당신이 젊은 아가씨가 되십시오.
if i knew
내가 알았다면
You are not willing to live your own life,
당신은 자신의 삶을 살고 싶지 않습니다.
I will punish you with house rules.
집 규칙으로 처벌하겠습니다.
I'll give you some lessons from women.
여성들에게 몇 가지 교훈을 드리겠습니다.
You have to copy them a hundred times first.
먼저 100번 복사해야 합니다.
Yes.
예.
in a few days,
며칠 안에,
Mr. Song from the Ministry of Justice will hold a promotion banquet.
법무부 송씨가 승진 연회를 열 예정이다.
Rong Yu and you will attend and bring some gifts
Rong Yu와 당신이 참석하여 선물을 가져올 것입니다
Represents the Rong family and Xingxiang Pavilion.
Rong 가족 과 Xingxiang Pavilion을 대표합니다.
Yes.
예.
【Astrology Center】
【점성술 센터】
The sky is blue and the earth is yellow.
하늘은 파랗고 땅은 노랗습니다.
The universe is boundless and time is boundless.
우주는 무한 하고 시간은 무한하다.
The sun rises and sets. The moon is round and waning.
태양이 뜨고 진다. 달은 둥글고 쇠퇴하고 있다.
The sky is full of stars.
하늘에는 별이 가득합니다.
Master, it’s time for you to turn the page.
스승님, 이제 페이지를 넘길 시간입니다.
OK
좋아요
That’s it for today.
오늘은 여기까지입니다.
Be sure to imitate the copybook carefully after returning home.
집에 돌아온 후에는 반드시 연습장을 꼼꼼히 따라해 보세요.
Next time we will learn new characters.
다음에는 새로운 캐릭터를 배워보겠습니다.
School is out. School is out. School is out.
학교는 문을 닫았습니다. 학교는 문을 닫았습니다. 학교는 문을 닫았습니다.
It's time to go home. Master. Master. Master.
집에 갈 시간이다. 주인. 주인. 주인.
Master.
주인.
Try this.
이 시도.
How do you give him cakes?
그에게 케이크를 어떻게 주나요?
Did you take a bite?
한 입 먹었나요?
I really can't resist
정말 거부할 수 없어
During class.
수업 중.
Master, have you learned all the Chinese characters in today’s lesson?
스승님, 오늘 수업에서 한자를 다 배웠나요?
Then there is no need to worry. I do not have either.
그렇다면 걱정할 필요가 없습니다. 나도 없어요.
Master, I studied very hard today.
선생님, 오늘 정말 열심히 공부했어요.
Can you reward me with my head?
내 머리로 보상해 주실 수 있나요?
Me too. Me too.
저도요. 저도요.
I also want to take a photo
나도 사진찍고싶다
Well, I don't have time to play with you today.
글쎄, 오늘은 너랑 놀아줄 시간이 없어.
I want to go back to be with my wife.
나는 아내와 함께 다시 돌아가고 싶다.
Why does your wife need company?
아내에게 친구가 필요한 이유는 무엇입니까?
Yes, why?
예, 왜요?
because,
왜냐하면,
Because she is unhappy.
그녀는 불행하기 때문입니다.
You can cheer her up with some candied hawthorn.
설탕에 절인 산사나무로 그녀를 격려할 수 있습니다.
You can also buy her a pet cricket.
그녀에게 애완용 귀뚜라미를 사줄 수도 있습니다.
Are you a dummy?
당신은 더미입니까?
We are fortune tellers.
우리는 점쟁이입니다.
We should use the methods learned in Astrology Pavilion to solve this problem.
이 문제를 해결하려면 점성술관에서 배운 방법을 사용해야 합니다.
Master, do you know when your wife’s birthday is?
선생님, 아내의 생일이 언제인지 아시나요?
I'll ask my dad to give your wife a prediction.
아버지께 아내에게 예측을 해달라고 부탁할게요.
See if there is any way to solve the wife's problem.
아내의 문제를 해결할 수 있는 방법이 있는지 살펴보세요 .
Little brother, this is not my wife.
동생아, 이 사람은 내 아내가 아니다.
She is the young master's wife.
그녀는 젊은 주인의 아내입니다.
We should call her the young lady.
우리는 그녀를 아가씨라고 불러야 합니다.
So, when is our young lady’s birthday?
그럼 우리 아가씨 생일은 언제예요?
She is not our young lady.
그 사람은 우리 아가씨가 아니거든요.
She is the young master's young wife.
그녀는 젊은 주인의 젊은 아내입니다.
It was December 22nd of the sixth year of Zhenyuan.
진원 6년 12월 22일이었습니다.
Isn’t there still three days left?
아직 3일이나 남지 않았나요?
Leave the divination to me.
점술은 나에게 맡겨주세요.
Master, isn't this a good opportunity?
선생님, 지금이 좋은 기회 아닌가요?
Are you ready for a fun birthday gift?
재미있는 생일 선물을 받을 준비가 되셨나요?
Make her happy?
그녀를 행복하게 해주나요?
Yes Yes.
예 예.
birthday present?
생일 선물?
???Under the sunset at dusk? ? ?
???해질녘 노을 아래서요? ? ?
???I traveled thousands of miles to a distant place? ? ?
???나는 먼 곳으로 수천 마일을 여행했다고요? ? ?
???Playing the piano under the moonlight? ? ?
???달빛아래 피아노 연주? ? ?
???These drinks won’t make me forget? ? ?
???이 음료수는 잊혀지지 않을까요? ? ?
???The desire I wrote for you? ? ?
???내가 당신을 위해 쓴 소망은요? ? ?
??? Our destiny is written on paper? ? ?
??? 우리의 운명은 종이에 적혀있다고? ? ?
??? Like the strongest wine? ? ?
??? 최강의 와인을 좋아하시나요? ? ?
??? There is no way to escape fate? ? ?
??? 운명을 피할 방법은 없나요? ? ?
???Looking back, I saw you waiting? ? ?
???뒤돌아보니 기다리고 있는거 보이시죠? ? ?
???Our life is full of joy and sorrow? ? ?
???우리의 삶은 기쁨과 슬픔으로 가득 차 있습니까? ? ?
??? Desire to crystallize into a bright galaxy???
??? 밝은 은하계로 결정화되기를 원하시나요 ???
???You quietly turned around and closed the marriage certificate? ? ?
??? 조용히 돌아서서 결혼증명서를 닫았나요? ? ?
???Ask how many stars are there in the sky? ? ?
???하늘에 별이 몇 개 있는지 물어보세요. ? ?
???The desire I wrote for you? ? ?
???내가 당신을 위해 쓴 소망은요? ? ?
??? Our destiny is written on paper? ? ?
??? 우리의 운명은 종이에 적혀있다고? ? ?
??? Like the strongest wine? ? ?
??? 최강의 와인을 좋아하시나요? ? ?
??? There is no way to escape fate? ? ?
??? 운명을 피할 방법은 없나요? ? ?
???Looking back, I saw you waiting? ? ?
???뒤돌아보니 기다리고 있는거 보이시죠? ? ?
???Our life is full of joy and sorrow? ? ?
???우리의 삶은 기쁨과 슬픔으로 가득 차 있습니까? ? ?
??? Desire to crystallize into a bright galaxy???
??? 밝은 은하계로 결정화되기를 원하시나요 ???
???I gently caress the guzheng, waiting for passers-by like you???
???나는 고젱을 부드럽게 어루만지며 당신같은 행인을 기다린다???
???So you are my indissoluble bond? ? ?
???그럼 당신은 나의 불용성 유대인가요? ? ?